Jules Langsner
Archives of American Art, Smithsonian Institution
- Printed Materials, circa 1960s, Series 5:; (Box 5; 2 folders)
  - Press Releases, circa 1960s (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Photographs, circa 1910s-1960s, Series 6:; (Box 5; 0.25 linear feet)
  Photographs are of people, places, works of art, and exhibitions. There are photographs of Jules Langsner, June Harwood, Philip Guston, Musa Guston, William Brice, Eddy Feldman, Rube Kadish, Stanton MacDonald-Wright, Frank Perls, and unidentified individual people and groups. Photographs of Langsner's travels include Japan, Korea, Taiwan, and other locations. Exhibitions pictured are California Art Club, "Black and White," "California Painters & Sculptors, 35 & Under," and unidentified exhibitions. Photographs of works of art are by William Turnbull, Jack Zajac, Walter Mix, Marion Aldrich, Roger Majorowicz, and Jasper Johns.
  - Oversize Photographs, circa 1950s-1960s (Box 4, Folder 51)
  - Photographs of Jules Langsner, circa 1930s-1960s (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Photographs of Jules Langsner with Others, circa 1910s-1960s (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Photographs of Family and Travel, circa 1940s-1960s (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Photographs of Exhibition Installations, circa 1940s-1960s (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Photographs of Works of Art, circa 1940s-1960s, (2 folders) (Box 5, Folder 7-8)
- Audio Recordings, 1954-1967, Series 7:; (Boxes 5-6; 0.25 linear feet)
  Audio recordings include four untranscribed 7" reel to reel audio recordings and one cassette tape. The reel to reel tapes are of two lectures by Langsner, You & Art/Berlin Party, and eulogies given at Langsner's funeral by Clement Greenberg, Henry Seldis, Peter Selz, Richard Brown, Donald Brewer, Tom Leavitt, Lorser Feitelson, Sam Francis, June Wayne, Gifford Phillips, and others. The cassette tape is a copy of the reel of eulogies.
  - You & Art/Berlin Party, 1954, April (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Unknown Lecture, 1967, (2 folders) (Box 5-6, Folder 10, 1)
  - Eulogies, 1967, October 5 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Audio Cassette Copy of Eulogies, 1967, October 5 (Box 6, Folder 3)
Other Finding Aid
Bibliography